{
  "quizzes": [
    {
      "title": "my-quiz",
      "courseName": "my-course",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "quiz-1",
          "answerA": "a-1",
          "answerB": "b-1",
          "answerC": "c-1",
          "answerD": "d-1",
          "correctAnswer": "a-1"
        },
        {
          "question": "quiz-2",
          "answerA": "a-2",
          "answerB": "b-2",
          "answerC": "c-2",
          "answerD": "d-2",
          "correctAnswer": "b-2"
        },
        {
          "question": "quiz-3",
          "answerA": "a-3",
          "answerB": "b-3",
          "answerC": "c-3",
          "answerD": "d-3",
          "correctAnswer": "c-3"
        },
        {
          "question": "quiz-4",
          "answerA": "a-4",
          "answerB": "b-4",
          "answerC": "c-4",
          "answerD": "d-4",
          "correctAnswer": "d-4"
        }
      ],
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "title": "asdf",
      "courseName": "asdf",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "asdf",
          "answerA": "asdf",
          "answerB": "",
          "answerC": "",
          "answerD": "",
          "correctAnswer": "asdf"
        }
      ],
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "title": "asdfdfsfsda",
      "courseName": "asdfdfasdf",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "asdfdfsa",
          "answerA": "asdf",
          "answerB": "",
          "answerC": "",
          "answerD": "",
          "correctAnswer": "asdf"
        }
      ],
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "title": "new-quiz",
      "courseName": "new-course",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "nq-1",
          "answerA": "na-1",
          "answerB": "n-b2",
          "answerC": "nc-3",
          "answerD": "nd-4",
          "correctAnswer": "",
          "selectedAnswer": ""
        },
        {
          "question": "nq-1",
          "answerA": "na-2",
          "answerB": "n-b2",
          "answerC": "nc-2",
          "answerD": "nd-2",
          "correctAnswer": "",
          "selectedAnswer": ""
        }
      ],
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "title": "yasin-quiz",
      "courseName": "yasin-course",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "q-1",
          "answerA": "a-1",
          "answerB": "b-1",
          "answerC": "c-1",
          "answerD": "d-1",
          "correctAnswer": "answerA",
          "selectedAnswer": ""
        },
        {
          "question": "q-2",
          "answerA": "a-2",
          "answerB": "b-2",
          "answerC": "c-2",
          "answerD": "d-2",
          "correctAnswer": "answerB",
          "selectedAnswer": ""
        }
      ],
      "id": 6
    }
  ]
}